<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<strings>
    <string key="T2R_Tuto_ShowVideo_Title">Tutorial Video</string>
    <string key="T2R_Tuto_ShowVideo_Message">A video explaining the basics of the game is available. Do you want to watch it before entering the interactive tutorial?</string>
    <string key="T2R_Tuto_ShowVideo_WatchButton">Yes</string>
    <string key="T2R_Tuto_ShowVideo_SkipVideoButton">No</string>
    <string key="T2RBubbleTuto_GameStart">Welcome to this interactive tutorial!\n\nSimply follow the instructions written on this board...

...Press the x button or hit this message to go on.</string>

    <string key="T2RBubbleTuto_GoalOfTheGame">In Ticket to Ride, your goal is to score the most points by:
- Playing TRAIN CARDS from your hand to claim ROUTES on the map
- Using these routes to connect cities listed on your TICKETS</string>

    <string key="T2R_BubbleTuto_ShowConductorNotes">You can push Geraldine’s help button at any time to read the detailed rules of the game.</string>

    <string key="T2R_BubbleTuto_SelectObjectivesAtStart">So let’s get started! Choose at least %d Ticket(s).
- Keep a Ticket pressed to highlight the cities it connects.
- Briefly press a Ticket if you want to select it.

Press Done to confirm your choice.</string>

    <string key="T2R_BubbleTuto_SelectObjectives">Choose at least %d Ticket(s). Briefly press a Ticket to select it.

Press Done to confirm your choice.</string>

    <string key="T2R_BubbleTuto_FirstTurn">Now let’s play your first Turn!</string>
    <string key="T2RBubbleTuto_IgnoreOpponents">For now, ignore your opponent(s).</string>

    <string key="T2RBubbleTuto_LookMap">Look at the map. We are going to help you claim your first routes
and complete the Ticket highlighted in blue.</string>

    <string key="T2R_BubbleTuto_PickThisFirstCardWithReason">Pick this card.
You will need a set of cards that matches the color and number of spaces of the route you want to claim.</string>

    <string key="T2R_BubbleTuto_PickThisSecondCardWithReason">Now pick this card.\nYou may only pick two cards during a single turn.</string>

    <string key="T2R_BubbleTuto_PickThisCard">Now pick this card.</string>

    <string key="T2RBubbleTuto_Locomotive">You just picked a Locomotive card; it acts as a wild.
You can use it to replace any card of color.
If you pick a Locomotive card face-up during your draw, it will be the only card you pick this turn.</string>

    <string key="T2R_BubbleTuto_PickCardFromStackWithReason">Now let's make a blind draw from the deck.</string>
    <string key="T2R_BubbleTuto_PickCardFromStack">Draw a card at random from the blind deck.</string>
    <string key="T2R_BubbleTuto_PickSecondCard">... and pick another one. Your turn is done!</string>

    <string key="T2RBubbleTuto_SelectMapAndRoute">Now select the map and claim the highlighted route.
Then choose the color you want to use to claim this route.</string>

    <string key="T2RBubbleTuto_ClaimRoute">Now let’s drop a %s card on the route highlighted to claim it.
Use the cross-hair that appears in the card’s corner to drag and drop it precisely on this route.</string>

    <string key="T2RBubbleTuto_ClaimRoute_Short">Now drop the %s card on the route highlighted to claim it.
The longer the route, the more points you earn.</string>

    <string key="T2RBubbleTuto_ClaimRouteAgain">Do the same again for the other routes on your Ticket!
Beware: If you fail to connect a Ticket's cities by game end, you will lose its points instead of gaining them!</string>


    <string key="T2RBubbleTuto_ColoredRouteClaimed">You just claimed a colored route.
These routes are claimed using a set of cards that all match the route's color.</string>

    <string key="T2RBubbleTuto_ShowScore">Your score is indicated here.</string>
    <string key="T2RBubbleTuto_ShowRemainingTrains">This is the number of trains you have left.</string>

    <string key="T2RBubbleTuto_ShowOpponentScore">Your opponent's score is located here.</string>
    <string key="T2RBubbleTuto_ShowOpponentRemainingTrains">Here is the number of trains your opponent has left.</string>

    <string key="T2RBubbleTuto_ShowOpponentNbCards">This is the number of cards in your opponent's hand.</string>
    <string key="T2RBubbleTuto_ShowOpponentNbTickets">The number of Tickets taken by your opponent is indicated here.</string>
    <string key="T2R_BubbleTuto_GameTurn">As you may have figured out by now, on each turn you can either draw two Train Cards or claim a Route.</string>

    <string key="T2R_BubbleTuto_FirstTicketDone">Congratulations, this Ticket is done.
The points indicated on it will be added to your score at game's end!

Successfully completing a Ticket during the game is a secret; keep it to yourself!</string>

    <string key="T2R_BubbleTuto_TryComplete2ndTicket">Try to complete another Ticket now.</string>

    <string key="T2R_BubbleTuto_AllTicketsDone">Congratulations, all your Tickets are done!
Now you may want to push your luck and draw some new Tickets; simply press the Tickets stack.</string>

    <string key="T2R_BubbleTuto_GameTurnWithTickets">Drawing additional Tickets is the third possible, alternative, action you may choose on your turn.</string>
    <string key="T2RBubbleTuto_TicketsCycling">You can cycle through your Tickets quickly by pressing the current one.</string>

    <string key="T2R_BubbleTuto_RunningLowOnTrains">You are beginning to run low on Trains.
Drawing some new Tickets now is probably too risky…</string>

    <string key="T2R_BubbleTuto_BlockYourOpponents">Once you or one of your opponents have 2 trains or less left in reserve, this will trigger the game’s last turn; so try to claim some routes quickly.
Block your opponents where you can!
You know enough now. Go ahead and finish the game on your own. Good luck!</string>

    <string key="T2R_BubbleTuto_ThreeLocos">There were 3 locomotive cards face-up so the game automatically wiped all cards out and drew 5 new ones to refresh the draw.</string>

    <string key="T2R_BubbleTuto_EndOfGame">Congratulations, you have just completed your first game!

Now the final scores are calculated, adding points for the Tickets successfully completed and subtracting points for those that failed.
Players with the longest path also get a 10-point bonus.</string>

    <string key="ColorName_purpleCard">purple</string>
    <string key="ColorName_whiteCard">white</string>
    <string key="ColorName_blueCard">blue</string>
    <string key="ColorName_yellowCard">yellow</string>
    <string key="ColorName_orangeCard">orange</string>
    <string key="ColorName_blackCard">black</string>
    <string key="ColorName_redCard">red</string>
    <string key="ColorName_greenCard">green</string>
    <string key="ColorName_locoCard">locomotive</string>
    <string key="ColorName_tunnelCard">tunnel</string>

    <string key="T2R_Tuto_StopTuto_Title">Stop the Tutorial</string>
    <string key="T2R_Tuto_StopTuto_Message">Do you really want to continue this game without the tutorial?</string>
    <string key="T2R_Tuto_StopTuto_QuitButton">Yes</string>
    <string key="T2R_Tuto_StopTuto_CancelButton">No</string>

    <string key="T2RBubbleTuto_ClaimFerry">Now drop a %s card on the Ferry route highlighted to claim it.

You must play a Locomotive card for each Locomotive symbol on the route.</string>
    <string key="T2RBubbleTuto_ClaimTunnel">Now drop a %s card on the Tunnel route.

3 cards will be drawn from the top of the Train cards pile.
For each card revealed whose color matches the color of the cards you played to claim the Tunnel, an additional card of the same color (or a Locomotive) must be played from your hand.</string>
    <string key="T2RBubbleTuto_FerryClaimed">You have successfully claimed a Ferry route!</string>
    <string key="T2RBubbleTuto_TunnelClaimed">You have successfully claimed a Tunnel route!</string>
    <string key="T2RBubbleTuto_RefusedToPayForTunnel">You didn't wish to pay more cards for this Tunnel route.

Try again later!</string>
    <string key="T2RBubbleTuto_FailedToClaimTunnel">You couldn't pay more cards for this Tunnel route.

Try again next turn!</string>


    <!-- Localization kit part 2 - 2015-09-24 -->
    <string key="T2RBubbleTuto_GreyRouteClaimed">You just claimed a gray route.
These routes can be claimed using any set of cards of a single color, provided you have at least as many cards of that color as the number of spaces in the route.</string>

</strings>
